What's up everybody? I want to show you
how to create AI videos that are
talking, whether they're of you or an
avatar of some kind that you want to
create. There's so many different ways
to do this now that are out there. And
so, I'm going to give you my workflow
that I found. Um, this isn't going to be
exhaustive, but it's going to show you
enough to get you playing around and get
it started. Okay. Now, a couple of tools
that you're going to need to do the
highest quality of this. Number one,
Higsfield. Higsfield AI is literally the
top dog when it comes to creating images
that look like people. And they have
their what's called Higsfield Soul
platform. What Higsfield Soul allows you
to do. I've created a couple different
versions for myself right here is they
allow you to and they don't all look
like me exactly, but they they are good
enough to create a character from videos
that I that I did right here. This was
like a Twitch streamer right here. Okay.
So, if I created this, this is one shot
right here that I could use. Here's a
couple of others. And what you can do is
here's some of my mom that we created.
Um, they have this thing called soul
character generator, which allows you to
upload
photos of yourself or a person, and then
it will generate a character that you
can use to generate any kind of photos
with this. And so that's something that
I think is really cool, uh, is the
ability to do this. Um, this is one
right here that I created. The prompt
was simply, uh, close-up selfie style,
someone casually at a desk, chair,
iPhone photography. Okay.
So, we what we can do is we can actually
go ahead and we can either create a
video with this if we want to. And
here's a couple of videos that I
actually created the other day.
which was a man walking towards a
camera. This is again to represent me.
This is a man in a forest with a
flamethrower. So, the way that you do
this is you literally again go ahead in
Higsfield go to the soul generator.
You're going to have to create an
account with Higsfield. The pricing is
pretty reasonable for what they give you
to create your account. Um I have the
ultimate plan, but you can also do
pretty much the same with the pro plan.
And they also have the sole character
creation in the $9 month plan. This just
gives you a lot more generations and
things like that. Okay. So then you can
create an image by describing what it
is, what the scene is. They also do have
this version right here. I was testing
this one iPhone version. I think it does
some weird things to my face. And so if
I go ahead and I generate this without
doing that iPhone version, this might
look a little bit more like me. Some of
these don't look exactly like me. Some
of the face is a little off, but it's
pretty cool as far as what it's able to
do. Like, I think that one actually does
kind of look like me, but I look a
little bit like I smoked some weed or
something in that photo.
I guess it fits the prompt, though. Um,
so anyways, you literally just describe
whatever you want in this. Now, here's
the other thing that you can do is you
can actually duplicate photo shoots that
you've seen that are around the web. And
this is a method that I love right here.
And so if I take this and I go um Twitch
video game streamer, this is just an
example of this right here. And I go
images. Okay.
I can actually take an image
of someone.
Here's one right here. This is good.
I can take this image, copy it into chat
GPT. So I screenshotted it and I said
describe this image in detail as if you
are describing a scene to recreate
recreated in a
AI photo generation app.
Okay.
And so what this is going to do is this
is going to create a description
of
this photo right here. So we're going to
pause this. All right. Copy and paste
description. A mid shot of a male gamer
streamer sitting at his desk. Okay.
Perfect. So we can actually take this
prompt right here that this generated
and we can paste this into Higsfield.
Turn off prompt enhance
and see as well what this generates from
that prompt.
This one actually came out a little bit
better off of this. I don't like the
thinning on the face that it's doing.
This one's pretty decent right there
still as well. So then in Higsfield once
you do that you can open up the video
generator. So any image you can turn
into a video. So what we'll do is again
we'll go under our images that we
generated here. They don't take a long
time to generate.
And then we could say okay generate a
video.
So I might say is man talking on camera
at Twitch stream
station.
I can generate up to 10 seconds of a
video.
And then there's a tool that I can
actually use called 11 Labs right here.
11 Labs allows you to actually clone
your voice. And this is really
incredible that it's able to do this. It
actually has a thing now where it
verifies that it actually is your voice.
So there's not like deep fakes and
things like that. So what I do is I
created a voice for myself using their
pro voice creation tool called create a
voice clone right here. Provoice clone.
I uploaded almost two hours of audio of
me talking and then I was able to create
a voice clone. I can say I love creating
AI videos that are clones of me and I
don't even have to record on camera.
And then I'll press generate speech and
you can hear it. It's really quick. I
love creating AI videos that are clones
of me and I don't even have to record on
camera.
It's It's pretty good. It's not perfect,
but it's pretty good. I mean, that's
that like I'm I'm liking it. I'm a I'm a
fan of the quality of that. Okay, so
there's that right there. So, now this
is going to generate us a video that we
can pull into
another app and use. You can do all of
this in in um
Higsfield. However,
uh there's another app that I also like
to use for this. So, we'll show you both
workflows. in Higsfield. If I click on
speak right here,
I can actually take the image
we use. Whoopsie.
Yeah. So, it's making me
do an avatar or upload an image. So, if
I actually go to my images that I
generated.
So, we'll go back to the uh like the
Twitch streaming
right here.
Say we use this one. We click on speak
instead of video. It's going to load
this up. And then I can actually upload
that audio that 11 Labs created us.
So I can upload this audio right here.
Okay.
I can go ahead and select it once it's
done uploading.
Go. We'll click on generate a man in
chair talking about
how he likes making AI videos. Okay, so
there's this version right here that
does this. Um, they also let you use
what's called ClingSpeak.
And ClingSpeak, I think, is a little bit
better quality. There's another app as
well called Cling. And you can use
clingai.com to do this. Clingai is one
of the highest quality video AIs that is
out there that exists. Okay, so keep
that in mind as well.
Um, and the reason why we like Cling is
it also has a
it's really one of the high one of the
highest quality video AIs. If you want
to create AI uh
films, cling is the one that you want to
use for this for quality. Okay. But I
can go right here under video and they
actually have this is where you can that
fear is costing you. There a couple I
made. Have you ever hovered over send or
rewritten a post the other day? If I
click on avatar, I can go under lip sync
and then what they let us do is they let
us upload a video to add lip sync to.
Okay, so that's that's why what we're
doing is we're generating videos and
then we're able to create lip sync on
top of those videos. So here's a video.
This is the video it made.
And again, doesn't look perfectly like
me, but it's good enough to create some
kind of a
uh
a combo with this.
Okay. So, we're going to save this
and then we could go into cling. We can
upload that video right here. Here's
that video.
Okay, we're going to upload this
detecting character. We go
and then you upload a file for dubbing.
This is our 11 Labs video file right
here.
It's going to add this audio right
there.
Want to add this speech.
Press generate.
And now it is generating. It'll take
about three minutes to lip sync my AI
generated audio to that video clip that
we generated. Let's see how Higsfield is
doing with some of the speech ones that
we also did over here. Uh Higsfield is
running these as well to give us kind of
some generations. Here's one I did the
other day.
Have you ever hovered over send or
rewritten a post 10 times?
>> I don't like the quality on that.
Have you ever hovered over send or
rewritten a post 10 times because you're
afraid it's too much?
All
right. So, I went ahead and here's one
of the I love creating AI videos that
are clones of me and I don't even have
to record on camera. So, again, the face
is a little off. I think it might have
been the angle. I did a couple here over
in Clling as well or in Pigsfield. I
love creating AI videos that are clones
of me and I don't even have to record on
camera.
I love creating AI videos that are this
was the one that I generated from that
prompt
in um
that actually does look like me a little
bit skinnier than I am but that actually
looks very very close even to my face
facial structure and everything. So,
those ones I actually like a lot the
quality of.
Made a couple of versions.
I love creating AI videos that are
clones of me and I don't even have to
record on camera. Even the the Higsfield
one is really good. I love creating AI
videos that are clones of me and I don't
even have to record on camera.
I love creating AI videos that are
clones of me and I don't even have to
record on camera. So, I think that one
is the one, the uh the cling one. Yep,
the cling one looks the best overall.
So, again, you can see how quickly
within just 12 minutes, we were able to
go ahead and create these different AI
videos, these different quality of
different things like this, different
tools that you can use for this. It
takes some trial and error. The first
time out, it doesn't always look perfect
and you got to tweak it, you got to tune
it, and that's where it can be a little
bit timeconuming as you play around with
this. But overall, this is amazing.
Being able to do this, being able to
create content like this is really cool.
Now, I like still creating content where
I'm recording a video. This is actually
me talking to you right now. But still,
this is really incredible being able to
use AI to create videos like this. And
so, check it out. Try it out for
yourself and see how it works.